A Guide to Records of the Secretary of Finance, 1998-2010 (bulk 2006-2009)
Library of Virginia
- Secretary of Finance: DOA. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: Payroll Service Bureau. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: Interest Earnings. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: Agency Legislation Prospects. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: Non-State/Walking Around. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: Finance. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: Secretary of Education-Higher Ed. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: Tech/Carilion Medical School. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: Other HIgher Ed. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Finance: HIgher Ed-Charge Card Rebates. (Box 39)
- Sec. of Ed. K-12: SOQ/Pre-K. (Box 39)
- Sec. of Ed. K-12: School Construction. (Box 39)
- Sec. of Ed. K-12: Virtual Virginia. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Natural Resources. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Public Safety. (Box 39)
- Secretary of Technology: Change Management. (Box 39)
- VITA. (Box 39)
- Oracle/VITA. (Box 40)
- Major IT Projects, 2008. (Box 40)
- EA Project Director. (Box 40)
- VEAP Cost Recovery Initiative, Mar. 2007. (Box 40)
- Idigent Care-Collection, June 2008. (Box 40)
- Small Employer Health Insurance Pilot, 2008. (Box 40)
- Medicare Part D Trans. (Box 40)
- Medicaid Expenditures, 2008. (Box 40)
- Mediaid MCO Rates, FY08. (Box 40)
- Governor's Health Reform Commission. (Box 40)
- Healthcare Reform. (Box 40)
- WQIF, 2006. (Box 40)
- SNR-Land Conservation and Fort Monroe Briefing to HAC/SFC, June 2008. (Box 40)
- CSU Funding, 2008. (Box 40)
- Sustainable Community Investment-EO69. (Box 40)
- 599 Study. (Box 40)
- Maximus 2007-VEAP. (Box 40)
- HB3202 Refunds, 2008. (Box 40)
- HB 3202, 2007. (Box 40)
- Transportation Portal, 2008. (Box 40)
- Transportation Authorities, 2008. (Box 40)
- Port Authority Bond. (Box 40)
- VA Port Authority, Apr. 2008. (Box 40)
- VA Veterans Taskforce-Workforce. (Box 40)
- Workforce-MOU. (Box 40)
- Workforce. (Box 40)
- Worforce Sub-Cabinet Meetings. (Box 40)
- Workforce Sub-Cabinet Meeting, Apr. 2008. (Box 40)
- Workforce Subcabinet, Feb. 2008. (Box 40)
- Workforce Subcabinet, Dec. 2007. (Box 40)
- Workforce Subcabinet, Mar. 2008. (Box 40)
- Lottery-Goldman Sachs, Dec. 2007. (Box 40)
- Lottery Proceeds Fund, 2008. (Box 40)
- Lottery-Revenue Update-Revised Forecast FY08, 08/10, 2007. (Box 40)
- Lottery. (Box 40)
- Lottery Fund RE SB 800. (Box 40)
- Lottery Sales-Monthly Data to HAC, 2008. (Box 40)
- Sallie May, July 2007. (Box 40)
- Travel Reimbursements. (Box 40)
- Pics. (Box 40)
- Productivity Measures. (Box 40)
- Focus Conference, Nov. 2008. (Box 40)
- Credit Exposure, July 2008. (Box 40)
- Bond Rating Press Release. (Box 40)
- Bartlett, et al, v. Commonwealth, et al. (Box 40)
- DOA-GF Preliminary Annual REport (Unaudited), FY06. (Box 40)
- Medicaid-Pediatric Rate Increase FY07/FY08, 2006. (Box 40)
- CGI-AMS Receivables (Transaction Fees for Vendors), Oct. 2006. (Box 40)
- NASBO-OPEB Preliminary State Estimates, 2006. (Box 40)
- JLARC-VA Community Action Partnership (VACAP), 2006. (Box 40)
- C and T Initiatives, 2006. (Box 40)
- Tax-Revised Revenue Impact of FED Legislation, 2006. (Box 40)
- Taxation Issues, 2006. (Box 40)
- SWAM Financial Services Forum, 2006. (Box 40)
- MATPERS Conference, Sep. 2007. (Box 40)
- Performance Management Group at VCU. (Box 40)
- NGA Summit on Transportation Funding and Finance. (Box 40)
- COVITS. (Box 40)
- Council of Presidents-Unified Amendment, 2008. (Box 40)
- Univ. Mary Washington Debt Policy, 2007. (Box 40)
- Virginia Tech/Carilion MOU, 2008. (Box 40)
- SCHEV Study-VCU Med. Building, Nov. 2007. (Box 40)
- Biotech Research Park, 2008. (Box 40)
- SCHEV Council Meeting, May 2008. (Box 40)
- Higher Ed. FY07 SWAM Expenditures, 2008. (Box 40)
- Eastern VA Medical Authoriy, 2008. (Box 40)
- Higher Ed. Base Adequacy, 2006-2007. (Box 40)
- Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, Nov. 2008. (Box 40)
- GABE. (Box 40)
- GABE, Oct. 2007. (Box 40)
- GACRE, Feb. 2008. (Box 40)
- GACRE Memo, 2008. (Box 40)
- VPSA Broadband, 2008. (Box 40)
- EO69, 2008. (Box 40)
- Housing History and Forecast. (Box 40)
- GACRE Meeting, Sep. 2008. (Box 40)
- CEPI. (Box 41)
- Higher Educ.-Level II Files Craig Burns/C. Davis, 2008-2009. (Box 41)
- COG Plan-SOF. (Box 41)
- ARPA Requests, 2009. (Box 41)
- FOIA Requests, Feb. 2008. (Box 41)
- Disparity Study, 2009. (Box 41)
- Management Standards Letters-Universities. (Box 41)
- SOF Strategic Plan (all agencies), 2010-2012. (Box 41)
- SOF Accomplishments (in agency), 2008. (Box 41)
- Ltrs Local Gov RE Budget Concerns (Resolutions), 2009 Sess. (Box 41)
- SCHEV Reports-Tuitions and Fees. (Box 41)
- Scheduling Requests. (Box 41)
- VPSA Budget, 2008. (Box 41)
- Management Agreement. (Box 41)
- COOP Meeting, OCP, July 2007. (Box 41)
- DPB Budget Reductions FY09/FY10, 2008. (Box 41)
- Management Standards Letter, 2008. (Box 41)
- Reports to General Assembly, 2008. (Box 41)
- GACRE, Nov. 2009. (Box 41)
- WF Sub-Cabinet Meeting. (Box 41)
- Congresional Briefing Papers, 2009. (Box 41)
- Agency Submissions-Drafts. (Box 41)
- General Provisions Review, 2009. (Box 41)
- Interview with David Jeippe re: Sec. Brown, Sep. 2009. (Box 41)
- Meeting with Michael Cassidy, Oct. 2009. (Box 41)
- ARRA Higher Ed. (Box 41)
- VNDIA Grants FY10, Meeting with R. Brown/DPB. (Box 41)
- All GACRE Meeting Minutes/Agendas. (Box 41)
- Reports, 2009. (Box 41)
- GABE and GACRE 2009. (Box 41)
- 2008 GACRE Meeting, Sep. 2008. (Box 41)
- Archiving/Records Retention. (Box 41)
- Archiving Records-Warner Files. (Box 41)
- Agency Strategic Plan-Dept. of Accounts, 2010-2012. (Box 41)
- Agency Strategic Plan-Dept. of Taxation, 2010-2012. (Box 41)
- Agency Strategic Plan-Dept. of the Treasury, 2010-2012. (Box 41)
- GABE, Oct. 1998. (Box 42)
- GABE, Oct. 1999. (Box 42)
- GABE, Dec. 2001. (Box 42)
- Governor's Advisory BOard of Economists, 2002. (Box 42)
- GACRE, Oct. 2003. (Box 42)
- GACRE, Nov. 1995. (Box 42)
- GACRE, Nov. 1996. (Box 42)
- GACRE, Nov. 1997. (Box 42)
- GACRE, Nov. 1998. (Box 42)
- GACRE, Nov. 1999. (Box 42)
- GACRE, Nov 2000. (Box 42)
- GACRE, Aug. 2002. (Box 42)
- GACRE, Nov. 2002. (Box 42)
- GACRE, Nov. 2003. (Box 42)
- Joint Money Committe Meeting, Aug. 1991. (Box 42)
- Joint Money Committe Meeting, Aug. 1992. (Box 42)
- Joint Money Committe Meeting, Aug. 1993. (Box 42)
- Joint HAC/SFC/HFC Meeting, Dec. 1993. (Box 42)
- HAC/SFC/HFC Joint Meeting, Aug. 1994. (Box 42)
- HAC/SFC/HFC Joint Meeting, Dec. 1994 (Box 42)
- Joint HAC/SFC/HFC Meeting, Aug. 1995. (Box 42)
- HAC/SFC/HFC Joint Meeting, Dec. 1995. (Box 42)
- HAC/SFC/HFC Joint Meeting, Aug. 1996. (Box 42)
- HAC/SFC/HFC Joint Meeting, Dec. 1996. (Box 42)
- HAC/SFC/HFC Joint Meeting, Aug. 1997. (Box 42)
- HAC/SFC/HFC Joint Meeting, Dec 1997. (Box 42)